Guide to the Norma L. Kelsey Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Norma L. Kelsey papers, approximately 1970-2010; 6231-001; 12.01 cubic feet 10 boxes
  - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILES, 1974-2009; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 1/11-4/8)
    - PUBLICATIONS, 1980/2010; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 9/16-10/14)
      - Office and Professional Employee International Union publications, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - King County Labor Council. Labor's Voice (newsletter), 1997-2003 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens. Senior News (newsletter), 1998-2001 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans. The Retiree Advocate (newsletter), 2001-2005 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Puget Sound Alliance for Retired Americans. The Retiree Advocate (newsletter), 2007-2009 (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Contra Watch, 1986 (Box-folder 10/6)
      - El Estiliano, 1990 (Box-folder 10/7)
      - For Peace and Solidarity, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - Gente, 1991 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - The Monitor, 1987 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Somos, 1985 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Trabajadores, 1985 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Nicaragua publications, 1980, undated (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Laboreport on Latin America, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 10/14)
- Norma L. Kelsey video recordings and papers, approximately 1997-2018; 6231-002; 0.65 cubic feet 1 box
  VHS Videotapes of news coverage of Norma Kelsey, World Trade Organization protest (1999) news coverage and Accountability Commission tapes; Common Sense Economics Trainings; Office and Professional Employees International Union training tapes; and a video from Washington State Jobs With Justice. Print materials include a 2017 Pacific Northwest Labor History Association calendar; a speech on Kelsey's rank and file reform of OPEIU Local 8, and OPEIU Local 8 meeting materials and local information.
  VHS video recordings.
  VHS cassettes are open for previewing onsite in the Special Collections Reading Room only.
  - Papers, 2016-2018
    - OPEIU "Working Together" Issue, 2016 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Labor History Calendar, 2017 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - OPEIU Local 8 meeting materials, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - VHS Tapes, 1997-2000
    - Institue for Community Leadership: Leadership Nonviolence Workshop, undated (Box 1)
    - OPIEU Convention Opening "Leadership", 1998 (Box 1)
    - WTO ARC - Panel Two Report, Aug 2000 (Box 1)
    - WTO ARC, Sept 2000 (Box 1)
    - WTO ARC, July 2000 (Box 1)
    - WTO Accountability Review Committee, Aug 2000 (Box 1)
    - Washington State: Jobs with Justice "Fighting Back", 1997 (Box 1)
    - Common Sense Economics: Module #1: The Economy is not like the Weather, undated (Box 1)
    - Economics Education: Module #2: Four Role Plays, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Norma on King TV; Norma on Town MTG, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Norma on King TV Town Meeting, 1998 (Box 1)
    - El Salvador; Edan Pastora Bombing, Frontline; Fire from the Mountain, undated (Box 1)
    - National Partnership Video Conference, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Telenoticiero "Extravision", undated (Box 1)
    - The Battle in Seattle video slideshow (Collective Media), undated (Box 1)